cmswire.com 2019-10-19

# Privacy Policy - Simpler Media Group

Simpler Media Group (the publisher of the CMSWire.com website) also referred to as “SMG” provides this Privacy Policy to inform users of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information received from users of our websites, located at [www.simplermedia.com](http://www.simplermedia.com/), [www.dxsummit.com](http://www.dxsummit.com/), [www.dwexperience.com](http://www.dwexperience.com/) and [www.cmswire.com](http://www.cmswire.com/) (“Sites”) or collected through our other services, including via email subscriptions and survey tools (“Services”).

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason; each version will apply to information collected while it was in place. We will notify you of any material changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy on this website. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.

By using our Sites and Services you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us.

## Respecting Your Privacy

We respect your privacy and dislike spam as much or more than you do. All of our email communications strive for 100% compliance with the [2003 CAN-SPAM Act](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/CAN-SPAM_Act_of_2003). We will never sell, rent, lease or give away your information (name, address, email, etc.) to any third party unless you explicitly consent to this during the process of providing this information. The exception to this practice is detailed below in the section entitled “Third Party Sponsors”.

If you sign-up for our email alerts service, then we will send you emails relating to the mailing list(s) or service(s) you joined, as well as marketing offers from our partners from time to time.

Financial information, such as credit card numbers and expiration dates, is used only to charge you for the service you are purchasing. This will never be given to any third party (other than our credit card authorization processor).

## Protecting Your Information

In order to prevent unauthorized access, we use strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given to us. We take all reasonable precautions to ensure the security of personal data stored on our system.

## Sharing of Information

Your personal information is being provided only to SMG (the publisher of this website) unless we specifically state otherwise (e.g., by indicating that a piece of content or an event is sponsored by a third party).

We will not disclose your personally identifiable information to any person or company except where you have given us permission to do so or if the law requires it, or where in good faith we believe such action is necessary to comply with a legal process. The exception to this practice is in the case of third party sponsors of content or events (see below).

We do not share or “rent” our newsletter subscriber list.

## Third Party Sponsors

If you have elected to register for one of our sponsored webinars or events, or to access sponsored research or content from SMG, we may share your Information (including Personally Identifying Information) with business partner(s) and/or sponsor(s) of the webinar, event, research and/or content.

By registering for this content or these events you agree that these sponsor(s) and/or business partner(s) may use your Personally Identifying Information to contact you to provide additional information about their products or services.

## Use of Cookies

Cookies are pieces of information that an interactive service (e.g., website, digital TV, etc.) transfers to your hardware (e.g., computer, mobile phone, set-top box, etc.) for record keeping purposes.

We do use cookies in our websites. In order to use the full functionality of the CMSWire.com websites, you should enable cookies for “cmswire.com”, “dxsummit.com”, “dwexperience.com” and “simplermedia.com”.

We use cookies for general web analytics purposes and also to optimize your experience when visiting this website. For example, if you have already taken a survey, we do not want to prompt you a second time to take the survey. If you are already signed up for our newsletter, we do not want to bother about signing up again.

Our goal is to use to cookies to improve the quality of your visits to our websites. The information we store in our cookies is not viewable by third parties. We do not store Personally Identifying Information in our cookies.

## Non-personally Identifiable Information

The SMG Sites also collect and use information in aggregate form to track the number of visitors to each page of the Sites, the visitor’s IP address and other technical information. This technical information does not by itself identify a specific individual. We use this data to understand how the SMG Sites are being used, what content is popular, what browser sizes are most common, etc.

## Third-party Web Beacons

We use third-party web beacons from Google, LinkedIn, Adobe/Marketo and other similar software, to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our Sites. These service providers may also use anonymous information about your visits to our Sites and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

## Opting-out of Email

If you would like to be removed from our database, please let us know. You may opt out of receiving future mailings from our mailing lists at any time. We always include a link in the footer of our emails for this purpose.

## Children

Our Sites and Services are targeted at a professional audience interested in information technology topics. We do not aim to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age. If we are made aware that information is or has been submitted by or collected from a child aged 12 or younger, we will delete this information.

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of Simpler Media Group, or your dealings with us, please contact us directly. We are happy to hear from you.

## Public Information

If you post any personally identifiable information in a Simpler Media Group website — for example, in a comment or a job posting — then this information may be displayed publicly.

## Policy Changes

This Privacy Policy came into effect in 2009 and was last updated on August 14, 2019. Any updates to this policy will be published on this page.
